[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Lily] Just a little longer,
and we'll finally be free.
We can finally be together.
[Diego] I can't wait anymore.
[Helena] All my money got incinerated!
Why not? All those booby traps
you set were all defective!
That's the reason why the fire started!
[Magbanua] That happened in the next town.
Someone made it rain money.
Do you know who's behind this?
[Magbanua] Our people
saw Lily Cruz and Diego Torillo
giving your money away to the people.
[Diego] I have to go.
I've got something to do.
Somewhere special.
Do you mean you'll propose to her?
[Diego] I'll tell you about it
tomorrow. I have to go.
-[Arnaldo] Sure thing. Take care!
-[Diego] Take care!
[Lily] Whatever happens tomorrow
or in the days to come,
there's only one thing I'm sure of.
We'll always be together.
I was planning on giving this to Lily.
I'll only propose to her
if you give me your blessing.
Of course, you have my blessing!
[Emilia] Mama and I
have a job for you. Let's go.
[Julio] I will help you crush Lily Cruz.
We have to help each other.
-[Julio laughs]
-[Emilia] Aw!
[Emilia] I love my family.
Papa, I heard Mama's money
has been burnt to ashes.
[sighs] That's right.
[tsks] So, what now?
The wealth you've been
gloating about. It's all gone.
[chuckles]
Do you know who burned the money?
Lily Cruz and your bastard son, Diego.
He just signed his death sentence.
So, go after my son then.
But if you do, you'll have to
answer to me. I swear it.
[chuckles]
You know, Raul, you shouldn't make
promises you can't really keep.
Why don't you just stick
to what you're actually good at?
Womanizing!
[laughs]
You know, Raul, I can
define you in four letters.
NG and GN.
No good, and good-for-nothing.
[laughs]
[continues laughing]
[Julio sighs]
[woman] Red Dragon won't be
happy to hear about this.
I've served her almost my whole life.
I think she would respect my decision…
to retire and live in peace.
Why are you doing this?!
Red Dragon gave you everything you needed!
You're living a good life because of her!
Why are you leaving?
This isn't the life I want
for my loved ones.
Tell Madam Red Dragon to start
looking for my replacement.
I don't want to be the Jaguar.
And I'm done being a criminal.
[tense music playing]
Move!
[soft instrumental playing]
You'll enjoy this date.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah. I'll make sure of that.
Where are we going?
Lily. Thanks for helping me out.
No worries. I got you! [chuckles]
-[Diego] How do I look?
-[Loring] Great!
That's the Diego we know.
He never gives up.
No matter how many times
she turns me down.
You'll never say die!
[Pandoy and Loring laugh]
I love her.
Nanny, Uncle…
I wish you were here.
[exhales]
[romantic music playing]
You look beautiful.
Charmer.
[Lily] This place looks nice.
You look even better.
[chuckles lightly]
Thank you.
What?
Come on.
-Thank you.
-I wanted to set things up
in our secret garden, but it rained.
-This place is nice too.
-And you really are beautiful.
[Lily chuckles]
Diego. Really, this place looks great.
Not compared to you.
Fritters? Fried bananas?
That's our favorite.
Nanny Loring used to cook that, remember?
Yes. How could I forget, Diego?
Actually, now I remember
why you had such chubby cheeks back then.
You couldn't stop eating fritters.
Your cheeks were so cute.
Wow! I wasn't expecting a throwback photo.
Imagine, Lily.
We've been through a lot.
We've been together for a long time.
But then, the reason why we're here…
is because I have something
important to tell you.
I know you still want us
to finish the fight…
before we fulfill our promises
to one another.
But, Lily, what if something happens
tomorrow or the next day?
What if we don't have a happy ever after?
Diego.
What are you talking about?
Don't say that.
Lily, we can't know for sure.
You know that, right?
We don't have any control over the future.
But we have tonight.
I'll prove to you that, despite
the challenges in life,
we can still keep loving each other.
Lily, I already lost you once.
I don't want to lose you again.
You won't. You won't
lose me again. I promise.
I want to spend the rest of
my life with my best friend.
You're everything to me.
[upbeat romantic instrumental]
Lily Cruz…
Will you marry me?
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" by playing]
Will you??
I will…
Of course!
Yes, I'll marry you.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" continues playing]
I love you so much, Lily.
I love you too, Diego.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" continues playing]
[song fades]
[ominous music playing]
[Diego] You might be hungry. Let's eat.
Go on. Have your moment.
I'll give you tonight.
But, tomorrow is a whole different story.
Camia, I want you to--
I want you to know that I'm the Jaguar.
[soft piano music playing]
Damian.
You're so beautiful.
Shall we sit?
Thank you.
Damian?
Why? Is there something wrong?
Camia, I need to tell you something.
I don't want to hurt you.
So, before anything else,
I want you to know that
I haven't been honest with you.
[pensive music]
What do you mean?
I never stopped being a criminal.
I'm the Jaguar, I worked for Red Dragon.
[exhales]
Camia, wait.
Please forgive me.
[pensive music continues]
Camia.
[whispering] Camia.
[tense music playing]
The once fearless Jaguar…
has now turned into a scared kitten.
No worries.
I'm going to take
both of you out of your misery.
[somber music playing]
[Damian] Camia, is there
anything I can do to help?
I'll do anything for you and Lily.
Camia, believe me. I've changed.
I'm not a criminal anymore.
I live a completely different life now.
These people are on a different level.
Why, Damian? Do you know Mercedes Palacio?
No, I don't know her.
Do you know anything about Red Dragon?
Are you part of Red Dragon's syndicate?
No. But I know of Red Dragon.
Damian, don't forget we all love you.
Whatever it is you're going through,
remember that we're ready
to fight with you,
as long as you stay true to us.
-Mom? Mom.
-Lily.
So, how did your date go?
-It was fine, Mom.
-Just "fine"?
Wasn't he--
What are you hiding back there?
Show me your hand.
-It's nothing, Mom. Really.
-Come on, let me see. Show me.
[soft music playing]
[exhales]
Diego and I are getting married.
I'm so happy for you, Lily!
And I'm sure your father is too.
I wish he was still here with us, Mom.
I miss him so much.
I miss him very much too.
How did your dinner with Uncle Damian go?
It was fine too. Lily.
My dear…
Cherish the love you and Diego hold, okay?
I want you to show the world
that there is no force greater than love.
We will, Mom.
I believe we will.
I have faith.
Honestly, dear,
I've already seen this ring.
I spoke to Diego.
I knew he was going to propose.
What? Why didn't you tell me?
That would've ruined
the surprise! [laughs]
I'm so happy for you, Lily.
I am too, Mom.
I'm so excited to be Diego's wife.
[giggles]
Sir! Let me go!
[pot breaks]
[Raul] I just want you to know
that nobody can keep us apart.
[Camia screams]
Dante, please forgive me
for hurting Camia.
I know you made our paths cross
again so I could protect her.
But I didn't expect my feelings
for her to return.
You used to say there's
always hope for change.
And now I know I'm ready to. For Camia.
I just pray she gives me another chance.
I hope she can forgive me
for all my mistakes.
[somber music playing]
Mom…
Mom. What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
It's nothing.
It doesn't look like it.
What happened? Tell me what's wrong.
Lily…
Your Uncle Damian told me something.
He's the Jaguar.
He worked for Red Dragon.
[soft instrumental playing]
It all makes sense now, Mom.
Now I know why the Jaguar saved me
when I was buried alive by the Ardientes.
Before Diego and the others found me,
Uncle Damian was at the scene.
Jaguar was there, he saved me.
It all makes sense now.
And if you think about it…
Uncle Damian sacrificed a lot for us.
He helped me bring down Red Dragon.
He protected you.
He protected me… and our entire family.
That's why even though he lied to us,
and kept secrets from us…
I'm grateful to him.
He looks out for us.
He protects us, Mom.
But it still hurts, Lily.
And I know you feel the same way.
But if there's one thing I'm sure of,
it's that your uncle
is changing for the better.
He's doing it for us.
Because we're what's left of his family.
Can you still forgive him, Mom?
He did ask me for my forgiveness.
Then can you still trust him?
-Diego.
-Mr. Damian.
Is Camia around?
She's inside, talking to Lily.
Please, come in.
Is something wrong?
I made a terrible mistake.
Lily. Auntie.
Mr. Damian is outside.
[soft instrumental playing]
[music fading]
[door opens]
[somber music playing]
Thank you for agreeing to talk to me.
I came here to tell you how sorry I am.
Camia, can you ever forgive me?
What you're asking for isn't easy, Damian.
I understand.
But I want you to know
I won't stop asking for your forgiveness.
From you and Lily.
I hope you can forgive me one day.
[ominous music playing]
Get down!
[gunfire]
-[Lily] Mom.
-[Damian] Wait!
-Wait!
-No! No!
-Who are you?
-No, wait!
[Lily] Diego.
[tense music playing]
[Camia] Lily!
[grunts]
-Come here.
-Let go of me!
-Hey!
-Lily!
-Mom, run!
-Lily, I can't just leave you!
-Go, now!
-It's dangerous here. Go on, Mom!
Lily!
[dramatic music playing]
Lily! Stop that! Let go of me! Lily!
-Who sent you here?
-Lily!
-Mom!
[suspenseful music]
Lily!
-[Lily] Diego.
-[Camia] Lily!
Diego.
[Camia shouting] Lily! Let me go! Lily!
-Hurry!
-Lily! Lily! Let go of me!
Camia!
[Damian] Camia!
-Camia!
-[gunshot]
Hurry! Let's go!
[suspenseful music playing]
[ominous music]
You're mine now.
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music playing]
Lily?
-Auntie?
-Diego!
-Lily!
[grunts]
-Mr. Damian!
-I've been shot.
-Careful now.
-Diego.
Find Lily and Camia
at the Ardientes' place.
I'll look for them
at Red Dragon's den! Go!
[engine roaring]
You, guard the other room. And you--
Lily!
Why did you let him in?!
-Lily! Auntie Camia!
-Stop there!
-Let go of me!
-Sir, enough!
Stop him!
Damn you, Ardientes!
Where are they?! Lily!
You won't shut up?!
-Lily!
-They're not here!
-Auntie Camia!
-Sir!
-Go on!
-Get him out of here!
Go on! Kill me! Lily! You bastards!
Let Lily go! Now! Lily!
What?! You idiot! What were
you going to do to my son?!
-Lily! Auntie Camia!
-What?! Hey! Let go of my son!
Get out of here!
[man] Let's go!
[Diego breathing heavily]
[door closes]
Dad, where are Lily and Auntie Camia?
Where are they?
I don't know, son. I have no idea.
-Don't lie to me.
-I really don't know.
The Ardientes aren't here either.
Then, where are they?
They took Lily and Aunt Camia!
I said I don't know! I don't know!
Then you're useless!
Diego! Where are you going?!
I'll look for them.
I'll get Lily and Auntie Camia back.
What happened to you, son?!
Why are you acting like this?
What happened to me?
Why am I acting like this?!
They've taken everything away from me.
I'm not letting them take Lily
from me too.
I won't let them.
Listen to me, Diego.
I know why you're acting this way.
I do.
This is all my fault.
Forgive me.
Please, forgive me.
I'm begging you…
Don't do anything rash.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
I promise I won't let you down
this time. I'll help you.
I'll help you find them, all right?
[Julio scoffs]
[Julio] Oh.
What's up, my boy?
[Julio] My son. My son of a gun!
You did good!
You did very, very good!
-Is she dead?
-Not yet, but she will be.
Aw.
Now, who is going to put
a bullet into Lily Cruz?
Me, I volunteer!
[scoffs] Baby girl, that's too easy.
After everything that Lily Cruz
has put our family through,
she deserves to suffer!
-Monster!
-I didn't mean it.
-You bastard!
-I don't love you!
-You love me.
-Mom.
-Lily, dear.
[Arnaldo] Tell me.
You are Lily Cruz, right?
-Answer me!
-Yes! I am! I am Lily Cruz!
-[Arnaldo and Lily scream]
-[gunshot]
-Emilia, that's enough!
-You can cross anyone,
but not me!
I'm not playing games with you!
Remember this, Emilia.
Remember this!
That's the last time you'll ever
get a chance to finish me off.
I won't hesitate to kill you.
[police officer] Emilia Torillo.
You are under arrest for plunder.
You can't do this to me!
Don't you know who I am?!
I'm Emilia Ardiente!
[Diego] Julio Ardiente!
I believe this is your money.
The money you used
to bribe Secretary Martel!
This is justice served
by the hand of Lily Cruz.
[in Spanish] Farewell, old man!
We will break her heart
while it's still beating.
[suspenseful music playing]
[whipping]
[Lily groans]
[Helena] We won't allow her to die
even if she begs for it!
-[whipping]
-[Lily groaning]
[Lily grunts]
What now, Lily Cruz?! Didn't I tell you?
If you play with a dragon's flame,
you'll get burned!
Now, die!
[laughs]
[Lily screams]
And when the fire dies down,
even her soul will bleed to death!
You're so cruel.
Harsh.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Helena] I didn't take
your resignation very well.
Once you're in, the only way out is death.
[Julio] I'll be sending you an address.
You have to be there within 20 minutes.
Because if not,
your precious love will die.
Let them go!
[Helena] If neither of you dies
within eight hours,
Lily and Camia will both die.
Only one of them can survive!
And only one of us can die!
And that's you!
[theme music playing]